AZAR BARFIPOUR

SUMMARY

Former software support specialist with a background in software engineering and 4+ years of experience looking for opportunities in front-end development. I have worked for large companies and have had the opportunity to work alongside excellent and impactful software teams. Currently, training to become a front-end developer and I am very eager to join an organization where I can have a great impact.

SKILLS

WEB: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Express, Mongoose, Node.JS, TypeScript

FRAMEWORKS, LIBRARIES AND ENVIRONMENTS: React.js, Angular, jQuery, SASS, Bootstrap

SYSTEMS, CMS AND DATABASES: Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, Firebase, PostgreSQL, SQLserver, MongoDB

PROJECTS

E-Commerce App Apr. 2022

An e-commerce React app for handicraft products, using Redux and Google authentication. Users can add to cards and remove

Technical specifications: React, Redux, HTML, CSS, Google authentication, Firebase

Weather-Location App May. 2022

A React app using API for checking weather by location. Users can see the weather by allowing access to their location. Moreover, users can check any place on the map.

Technical specifications: React, HTML, CSS, Google map API and Open Weather API

Feb. 2022 Meetup App

A book event application for searching and booking events

Technical specifications: React, HTML, CSS, Firebase

Mar. 2022 Portfolio Website

Technical specifications: HTML, CSS, BootStrap, JavaScript, jQuery

EMPLOYMENT

Front End Developer | Volunteer at Freelivenet, Vancouver

May. 2022 - Present

Testing and developing an Angular CRM working with Git and Bitbucket

Data Entry | Volunteer at Terry Beech Office, Vancouver

Jul. 2021

Analyzed people surveys and entered into the application

Software Support Specialist | Behban software Co, Tehran

Sep. 2015 - Oct. 2020

- Created more than 100 reports for many big companies from their data
- Worked with huge databases from one of the biggest oil company in Middle East
- . Debugged and solved more than 100 customers in each day and traveled around the country to install the app
- Created forms in ASP classic by using ASP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and SQL collaborating with multiple teams at company

EDUCATION

Web Development Diploma | CICCC, Vancouver, Canada

Aug. 2021 - Present

HTML, CSS, React.js, Node.js, SQL, Python etc.

UAP | University Canada West, Vancouver, Canada

Apr. 2021

Academic English course

Computer Software Engineering B.S. | UOK, Sanandaj, IRAN

Feb. 2015

Thesis: Web site design by Joomla Advisor: Fardin Akhlaghian